Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - Special Board Meeting, July 8, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1742)
    - Board Meeting, July 10, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1743)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 14, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1744)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1745)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 21, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1746)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 22, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1747)
    - Board Meeting, July 24, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1748)
    - Board Meeting, July 31, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1749)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1750)
    - General Meeting, August 9, 1953, 5 leaves (Box 14, Item 1751)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1752)
    - Board Meeting, August 21, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1753)
    - Board Meeting, August 28, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1754)
    - Board Meeting, September 4, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1755)
    - Board Meeting, September 11, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1756)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1757)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1758)
    - Board Meeting, October 2, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1759)
    - Board Meeting, October 9, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1760)
    - General Meeting, October 11, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1761)
    - Board Meeting, October 15, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1762)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1763)
    - Board Meeting, October 27, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1764)
    - Board Meeting, October 29, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1765)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1766)
    - Board Meeting, November 13, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1767)
    - Board Meeting, November 19, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1768)
    - Board Meeting, November 27, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1769)
    - Board Meeting, December 3, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1770)
    - Board Meeting, December 11, 1953, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1771)
    - Board Meeting, December 18, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1772)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1953, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1773)
    - Board Meeting, December 31, 1953, 3 leaves (Box 14, Item 1774)
    - Board Meeting, January 9, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1775)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1776)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 19, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1777)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1778)
    - Special General Meeting, January 24, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1779)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1780)
    - Board Meeting: Special to discuss Symphony Contract, February 2, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1781)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1782)
    - Board Meeting, February 12, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1783)
    - Board Meeting, February 19, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1784)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1785)
    - Board Meeting, March 5, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1786)
    - Board Meeting, March 12, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1787)
    - Board Meeting, March 19, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1788)
    - Board Meeting, March 26, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1789)
    - Board Meeting, April 1, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1790)
    - Board Meeting, April 9, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1791)
    - Board Meeting, April 15, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1792)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1793)
    - Board Meeting, April 30, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1794)
    - Board Meeting, May 7, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1795)
    - Board Meeting, May 14, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1796)
    - Board Meeting, May 21, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1797)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1798)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1799)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1800)
    - Special Board Meeting, June 23, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1801)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1802)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1803)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1804)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 13, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1805)
    - Board Meeting, July 16, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1806)
    - Board Meeting, July 23, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1807)
    - Board Meeting, July 30, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1808)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1809)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1810)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1811)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1812)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1813)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1814)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 14, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1815)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1816)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1817)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 28, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1818)
    - Board Meeting, October 1, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1819)
    - Board Meeting, October 8, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1820)
    - Board Meeting, October 15, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1821)
    - Board Meeting, October 22, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1822)
    - Board Meeting, October 29, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1823)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1824)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1825)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 15, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1826)
    - Board Meeting, November 19, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1827)
    - Board Meeting, November 26, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1828)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1829)
    - Board Meeting, December 17, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1830)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1831)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1832)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1833)
    - Board Meeting, January 17, 1955, 2 leaves (Box 14, Item 1834)
    - Board Meeting, January 21, 1954, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1835)
    - Special Board Meeting at Kleinhans Music Hall, January 21, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1836)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 25, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1837)
    - Board Meeting, January 28, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1838)
    - Special General Meeting, February 3, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1839)
    - Board Meeting, February 4, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1840)
    - Board Meeting, February 11, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1841)
    - Special General Meeting, February 14, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1842)
    - Board Meeting, February 18, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1843)
    - Board Meeting, February 25, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1844)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 1, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1845)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1846)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1847)
    - Board Meeting, March 11, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1848)
    - Board Meeting, March 19, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1849)
    - Board Meeting, March 23, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1850)
    - Board Meeting, April 2, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1851)
    - Board Meeting, April 9, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1852)
    - Board Meeting, April 16, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1853)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1854)
    - Board Meeting, April 30, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1855)
    - Board Meeting, May 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1856)
    - Board Meeting, May 14, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1857)
    - Board Meeting, May 21, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1858)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1859)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1860)
    - Board Meeting, June 14, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1861)
    - Board Meeting, June 17, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1862)
    - Special Board Meeting, June 21, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1863)
    - Board Meeting, June 24, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1864)
    - Board Meeting, July 1, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1865)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1866)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 12, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1867)
    - Board Meeting, July 15, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1868)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 19, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1869)
    - Board Meeting, July 22, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 14, Item 1870)
    - Board Meeting, July 29, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1871)
    - Board Meeting, August 3, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1872)
    - Board Meeting, August 5,1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1873)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1874)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1875)
    - Special Board Meeting, August 16, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1876)
    - Board Meeting, August 18, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1877)
    - Board Meeting, August 26, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1878)
    - Special General Meeting, August 28, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1879)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1880)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1881)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1882)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1883)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 20, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1884)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1885)
    - Board Meeting, September 29, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1886)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 1, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1887)
    - Board Meeting, October 7, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1888)
    - General Meeting, October 9, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1889)
    - Board Meeting, October 14, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1890)
    - Board Meeting, October 22, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1891)
    - Board Meeting, October 28, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1892)
    - Board Meeting, November 1, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1893)
    - Board Meeting, November 11, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1894)
    - Special General Meeting, November 13, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1895)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 16, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1896)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1897)
    - Board Meeting, November 25, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1898)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1899)
    - Board Meeting, December 17, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1900)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 19, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1901)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1902)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1955, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1903)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1904)
    - Board Meeting, January 6, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1905)
    - Board Meeting, January 13, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1906)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 13, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1907)
    - Board Meeting, January 20, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1908)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 25, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1909)
    - Board Meeting, January 27, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1910)
    - Board Meeting, February 3, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1911)
    - Special General Meeting, February 6, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1912)
    - Board Meeting, February 10, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1913)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1914)
    - Special General Meeting, February 17, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1915)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 21, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1916)
    - Board Meeting, February 25, 1956, 2 leaves (Box 15, Item 1917)
    - Special Open Board Meeting, March 5, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1918)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1919)
    - Special General Meeting, March 14, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1920)
    - Board Meeting, March 16, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1921)
    - Board Meeting, March 23, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1922)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 27, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1923)
    - Board Meeting, March 30, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1924)
    - Board Meeting, April 6, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1925)
    - Board Meeting, April 13, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1926)
    - Board Meeting, April 20, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1927)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1928)
    - Board Meeting, May 4, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1929)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1930)
    - Board Meeting, May 18, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1931)
    - Board Meeting, May 25, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1932)
    - Board Meeting, June 1, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1933)
    - Board Meeting, June 8, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1934)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1935)
    - Board Meeting, June 22, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1936)
    - Board Meeting, June 30, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1937)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1938)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 11, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1939)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1940)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1941)
    - Board Meeting, July 27, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1942)
    - Board Meeting, August 4, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1943)
    - Board Meeting, August 10, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1944)
    - Board Meeting, August 17, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1945)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1946)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1947)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1948)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1949)
    - Board Meeting, September 21, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1950)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 25, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1951)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1952)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 1, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1953)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 4, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1954)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1955)
    - Board Meeting, October 12, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1956)
    - General Meeting, October 14, 1956, 4 leaves (Box 15, Item 1957)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1958)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 23, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1959)
    - Board Meeting, October 24, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1960)
    - Board Meeting, November 2, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1961)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1962)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1963)
    - Board Meeting, November 30, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1964)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 4, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1965)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1966)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 10, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1967)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1968)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1969)
    - Board Meeting, December 28, 1956, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1970)
    - Board Meeting, January 4, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1971)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1972)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 15, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1973)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1974)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1975)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 30, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1976)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1977)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 5, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1978)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1979)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1980)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1981)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1982)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1983)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1984)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1985)
    - Board Meeting, March 26, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1986)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1987)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1988)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1989)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1990)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1991)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1992)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1993)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1994)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1995)
    - Board Meeting, June 5, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1996)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1997)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1998)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 1999)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2000)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2001)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2002)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2003)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2004)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2005)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2006)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2007)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2008)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2009)
    - Board Meeting, September 20, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2010)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2011)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2012)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2013)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2014)
    - General Meeting, October 13, 1957, 2 leaves (Box 15, Item 2015)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2016)
    - Board Meeting, October 25, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2017)
    - Board Meeting, October 30, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2018)
    - [Election of Officers] November 1, 1957, 2 leaves (Box 15, Item 2019)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2020)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 12, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2021)
    - Board Meeting, November 15, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2022)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2023)
    - Board Meeting, November 29, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2024)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 2, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 15, Item 2025)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 4, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2026)
    - Board Meeting, December 6, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2027)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2028)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2029)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2030)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 31, 1957, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2031)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2032)
    - Board Meeting, January 8, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2033)
    - Board Meeting, January 17, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2034)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2035)
    - Board Meeting, January 31, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2036)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 4, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2037)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2038)
    - Board Meeting, February 13, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2039)
    - Special General Meeting, February 14, 1958, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2040)
    - Board Meeting, February 21, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2041)
    - Board Meeting, February 28, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2042)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 1, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2043)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2044)
    - Special General Meeting, March 7, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2045)
    - Board Meeting, March 14, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2046)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 19, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2047)
    - Board Meeting, March 21, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2048)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 24, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2049)
    - Board Meeting, March 28, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2050)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 2, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2051)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 3, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2052)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2053)
    - Board Meeting, April 11, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2054)
    - Board Meeting, April 18, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2055)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2056)
    - Board Meeting, May 2, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2057)
    - Board Meeting, May 9, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2058)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2059)
    - Board Meeting, May 23, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2060)
    - Board Meeting, May 29, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2061)
    - Board Meeting, June 13, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2062)
    - Board Meeting, June 20, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2063)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2064)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2065)
    - Board Meeting, July 11, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2066)
    - Board Meeting, July 18, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2067)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 23, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2068)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2069)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 29, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2070)
    - Board Meeting, August 1, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2071)
    - Special Board Meeting, August 6, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2072)
    - Board Meeting, August 8, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2073)
    - Board Meeting, August 15, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2074)
    - Board Meeting, August 22, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2075)
    - Board Meeting, August 29, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2076)
    - Board Meeting, September 5, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2077)
    - Board Meeting, September 12, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2078)
    - Board Meeting, September 19, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2079)
    - Board Meeting, September 26, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2080)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 1, 1958, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2081)
    - Board Meeting, October 3, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2082)
    - Board Meeting, October 10, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2083)
    - Board Meeting, October 17, 1958, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2084)
    - Board Meeting, October 24, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2085)
    - Board Meeting, October 31, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2086)
    - Board Meeting, November 7, 1958, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2087)
    - Board Meeting, November 14, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2088)
    - Board Meeting, November 21, 1958, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2089)
    - Board Meeting, November 28, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2090)
    - Board Meeting, December 5, 1958, 3 leaves (Box 16, Item 2091)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2092)
    - Board Meeting, December 19, 1958, 3 leaves (Box 16, Item 2093)
    - Board Meeting, December 26, 1958, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2094)
    - Board Meeting, January 2, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2095)
    - Board Meeting, January 9, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2096)